Happy birthday to you.
November 11th?
Is that a special day?
I think I know. 11-11. Make a wish.
Pretty sure I'm gonna be busy around then.
I'm busy that day, and it's
something that I can't get out of.
Sorry, big sis.
Happy birthday to Yanni Neko.
Happy birthday!
I think we've rehearsed enough now.
I still can't believe she was
actually worried about her birthday.
I guess Yanni Neko has a soft side too.
Hey, uh, what is that thing?
I made this stuffed Yanni
as a present for her.
I used some of her real hair, which
made it look like she has a twin.
Isn't it cute?
Uh, yeah, totally.
Wait, that's...
Anywho, I wonder why
Yaninego isn't here yet.
Don't tell me nobody thought
to invite her to this.
Now wouldn't that just be a hoot?
Hmm?
Huh?
Oh!
I'm so sorry!
Thank you so much for watching.
Don't fall into можноBEHOW!
Got these words in love?
They died, not they Durham!
Don't fall into them! Don't
fall into normal destruction!
If it's over, if it's over, if it's
over, I'll just be able to do it.
If it's over, I'll just be able to do it.
3401!
Yeah!
Here we go!
Hey, is Kaoruko here?
A man?
Kaoruko, her first name? Huh?
Why are you freaking out so much?
Who are you?
How do you know Kaoruko?
What are you talking about?
Ah, I'm her boyfriend.
She has a boyfriend?
I've never even held
hands with a guy before!
She is such a traitor!
Wh-what do you want with her?
I brought her panties.
She's even doing it with this guy?!
Doggy style. Shower sex.
With cuddling after her.
They had a curiosity.
You a virgin.
Don't touch my penny!
Sorry, Hame.
Are you okay?
Ignore him.
He's a moron.
You're such a traitor! What did I do?
Sorry for the mix-up.
This jackass here is my little brother.
Hey there, the name's Shunran.
Nice to meet ya.
Do you have any idea how
much I hate you right now?
I'm sorry.
You made it too easy.
Goddammit!
You know what? Whatever.
So you're siblings then?
I figured it was that,
to be honest with you.
I mean, there's no way that you would
have a boyfriend, right, Kansai?
No, I wasn't gonna let you trick me!
Well, the truth is,
we're only half siblings.
That's incest!
Forbidden love? Quit it!
I promise you he's lying!
Hey, Nishi, do you want another drink?
Here, you can have some of mine.
It tastes better.
Would you guys leave her alone?
If anyone's going to get
her another drink, it's me.
You all are sweet.
I'm going to step away.
I'm going to go find the powder room.
No, don't leave us, Nishi.
I love you so much, Nishi.
How many times are you
going to say that to her?
I'll just pretend I didn't hear that.
I'm gonna smell like smoke. Huh? Nishi?
I thought you went to the bathroom.
Oh, yeah, well, I just
wanted to sober up a bit.
Um, yeah, so did I.
Chilly out here, huh?
Nishi, I wanted to say something.
You're really mature and
you're considerate as well.
You're also graceful.
I'm none of those things, though.
Oh, listen to you.
Come on, that's crazy talk. No, no.
I mean, I could never be
the organizer for a party.
I'm not really good at talking
to people like you are.
Well, the only reason I'm the organizer
is because I finished my thesis.
And I'm not that good
at socializing either.
Get away from me!
Sounds like a pervert alert.
Never a dull moment.
You wanna head back inside?
Yeah, I guess so.
What?
The pervert is burnt to a crisp!
Somebody catch her!
Yanni's the downtown pervert?
Were you cooking inside a volcano or what?
When you make a bonfire,
you gotta be careful.
Are you part fireman?
You should be burnt to a crisp!
Uh, hang on, Nishi.
Is this what you normally act like?
No, not really.
I wouldn't say it's normal.
Her name isn't Nishi, it's Kansai.
Shut your damn mouth!
Oh boy.
I...
You what?
I love this sight of you!
It's just that up until now, you were
so perfect it was hard to approach you.
But now that I've seen this, I really,
I really want you to be my friend!
Oh, really? Thank you.
Kansai, give me a cigarette.
Would you just go away? Huh?
You smoke even though you're
still a college student?
Um, now I wouldn't say that.
But I smoke too.
Just promise me you won't tell
anyone else about this, okay?
Your little cigarettes.
That's quite a choice
of brand you got there.
Anyway, I guess that's that, right?
So then we're...
how do you keep up the act it's definitely
not easy give me a
cigarette chain smoker cat
The first wind of spring.
This can't be happening!
That was three full days
worth of work! Shut!
The wind just blew away
my entire manuscript!
Your manuscript?
I have to say, you really
saved me back there.
If you hadn't shown up right then, I
for sure wouldn't have made my deadline.
Oh no!
I'm glad it happened, because now I get
to visit a professional's workplace!
Time really does fly, though.
That was a year ago, and we
blink and it's almost over.
It was a pretty eventful year.
Even though you're a published author,
you were still kind enough to give
advice to an amateur writer like me.
Oh, come on, stop it.
You look up to her way too much.
Well, yeah, of course I look up to her.
Tatsuro makes a living doing
something that she loves.
She's an inspiration to me.
Isn't that why you're working
as her assistant now, Yanni?
I've never actually read Tatsurou's manga.
I wish you'd read it at least once so
you'd remember the character's hair color.
Hang on, your own assistant hasn't
even read your books before?
Well, that's just not acceptable!
As a creator, that lack of awareness is...
Have you even read Mankasu's manga before?
Yeah, of course I have!
Well, I bought all of them, but I'm
just saving them to read another time.
It's okay.
I'm sure you've been busy.
Hmm.
Does she seriously still believe in Santa?
She's not the type to do
something all cute like that.
Maybe it's just a prank?
Whether you want to bet she asked
for cigarettes or something.
Jeez, she's the one who wanted to
have this Christmas drinking party.
Hi, Santa.
A nice smoking area for
Christmas would be nice.
You smoke with or without a smoking area.
Come on, that's not something
you can put in a stocking.
Oh, she wrote more on the back.
Oh, and smoking with my friends
in the sun would be great.
Oh.
Oh man, that made me kind of emotional.
I don't get it.
Who knew she had feelings?
Look at us doing the thing.
I have to say I'm beat.
I haven't played in
snow since I was a kid.
Hi guys.
I brought treats.
Sake and snow, my favorite.
This is super cozy.
Wouldn't be angry if we
did this again sometime.
Definitely.
Is the cold making these drinks stronger?
Oh, don't blame the cold.
It's just the booze.
Let a girl live a little.
I'll drink to that.
Woo-hoo!
Taking out the trash is a pain in the ass.
Huh?
Is that the smoking area made of snow?
Snow sculptures?
Oh, they're so elaborate.
Aren't you gonna rescue us?
Chainsmoker Cat.
I'm very sure if I keep drinking at this
pace, I'll be trashed before New Year's.
Don't pass out yet.
We still have to go to the shrine tonight.
Anyone who falls asleep loses.
This doesn't really taste like sake.
Yeah!
If anyone falls asleep,
then they have to shove their
underwear in the landlord's mouth!
You're a genius!
That's hilarious!
Now we have to stay away!
That's so gross!
You know you would love that!
We seriously can't fall asleep now!
I'm kinda sleepy!
Ch-Chain Smoker Cat, Ch-Chain
Smoker Cat, Cat, Cat,
Ch-Chain Smoker, Chain Smoker Cat!
All right, everyone!
Happy New Year!
Let the annual New Year's
mochi pounding begin!
Yanni Nickel!
I'll pound it!
You pour water on the
mochi and knead it! Got it?
I understand the landlord
being all excited,
but what's with Yanni being so fired up?
Maybe she got cigarettes his payment.
It's way too early in the
morning to be doing this!
Super Mochi Pound!
All right!
And hurt this!
Oh...
Been a while since I've showed
off my high-speed Mochi Pounding.
I guess I'm a little rusty.
Huh?
Where did Yanni Neko go?
Who knows?
Maybe she ran away.
Should have expected that from her.
Oh, well.
Once it cools down, we'll shape it. Sure.
Like this. There we go.
Am I getting red bean paste in these ones?
Yeah, those are going
to be the Mugwort mochi.
Did you know that Mugwort is said to
ward off evil spirits and misfortune?
Or as some call it, Yakku.
Don't you guys think this mochi kind
of looks like Yanni's hair color?
Don't say that.
It might start smelling like cigarettes.
All right, let's fire this up.
Yanni's echo!
How the hell did you get in there?
Ah, ah, oh, oh, it, it was a dream.
Hang on, that was my
first dream of the year.
It had bad omen written all over it.
Huh?
How long are you going to keep sleeping?
Can you wake up already?
Hurry up, it's time to pound some mochi.
Right, let's do it.
All right, everyone!
First of all, Happy New Year!
It's time for our building's annual New
Year's Mochi Pounding, Yanni Neko! Nya!
I'll pound it.
Your job is to pour water on the
mochi and knead it. Got it? Nya!
I understand the landlord
being all excited,
but what's with Yanni being so fired up?
Maybe he's paying her in
a bunch of cigarettes.
It's way too early in the
morning to be doing this!
Let's get it done, Yanni Neko!
Why'd you stop?
Is something wrong?
Well, it's just right.
Let's do this!
They said it was cigarette poisoning.
The poor thing was still so young.
Here's what I heard.
Apparently, a cigarette got mixed
into the mochi he was making.
Hurry up, it's time to pound some mochi.
Am I in a time loop?
It's time to pound some mochi.
Ah!
Pound the mojiii.
I don't know why it's happening,
but I keep repeating the day
of the mojibounding and...
Ah! Amigo!
Someone dies every time.
Each day starts off the same way.
What pounds the mojii?
I don't know how to escape
from this time loop.
However,
if I can just finish this mochi-pounding
peacefully without anyone dying,
then maybe...
The weather is awesome for New Year's Day.
Perfect for making mochi.
The landlord seems a
little bit sad, though.
So when do we get to eat this stuff?
Up until now.
Whenever they got close to the
mortar, a fatal accident would happen.
Very well.
I just need to do something crazy
enough to keep them all away from it!
Ahh!
What the hell are you doing?
Just go with balls out,
couple with the mochi.
That bass flopped around like
a fizzle just out of water!
They should keep everyone away!
Huh?
No, the cannon sticks are kicking in!
Yanni, don't touch it, it's giant!
Don't come any closer!
Yanni, no!
He's all stripes and no balls! It's done!
Eat it!
It was both soft and
hard at the same time.
The loop didn't start over.
Has it ended?
Am I the only one that knows
about this loop of fate?
You're Otani, right?
We just received a report.
Please come with us to the station.
It was...
the right thing to do.
Chainsmoker Cat?
Rise and shine!
I thought we'd go get some
Awachi Island burgers today!
It's the new year.
Can't we just relax a bit?
Relaxing was before eight.
It's time to get up!
And unless you plan on freezing
to death, we need more kerosene.
Quit lollygagging!
Go and get it!
Gosh, that's such a pain.
Hands off, you dung beetle!
Oh, for crying out loud!
No one's moving!
Traffic on a holiday.
I swear I'll tear all
these people a new one!
See how much Mom loves traffic.
She sure is loud with her love. You know,
ever since you started living in that
apartment, you've been acting more like her.
Take that back or a whoopperass!
Shut your damn mouths!
Oh, well, we haven't moved
an inch and I'm starving.
We're going home.
Seriously?
Here's your homemade Awaji Eileen burger.
There's nothing better than being at home.
You realize you're the
one who wanted to go out.
Kaoruko, did you put on a
few pounds over the holidays?
You want my old maternity clothes?
I'm not that big.
Do you want them, Shunran?
Why would I?
Oh, you do kind of have
a big butt, though, sis.
If you wear those clothes backwards,
the part that's for the belly
will fit over your butt.
Thanks for the food.
There's more burgers if
you want. No, thanks.
I'm a cow, remember?
I'm done, too.
You're not going anywhere!
After we eat, it's family time!
You crazy?
Why don't we all play a board game
together and watch Shinkie Geckie?
Oh no, we haven't been back home in a
good while, so Mom's all needy, isn't she?
Okay, I have an idea. You do?
I've been working on my beatboxing.
I don't give a rat sass about that.
Now if you lose, that means
you gotta stay longer!
Hooray!
Let's get this going!
I'll dump them shit, darling!
I'm sick of this goddamn house!
Boom, boom, hello, I'm Sooneran.
Kiko no yukamu
Kyou no e 지방 Obu shi no ichi
da wa ni Soto ni zaai yoi Nee,
isu mo doori no hito Koko
orde kewa Koko orde kewa Sato
bata ni takia Udo kama shiito
wa Kami sugi tat Gam no aji so
Thank you.